let quiz = [
    {
        para: "The Yuddha kanda (also referred to as Lanka kanda) is one of the main episodes in the great epic Ramayana. The Yuddha Kandam narrates the Ramayana War between the army of Rama and the army of Ravana. Having received Hanuman's report on Sita, Rama and Lakshmana proceed with their allies towards the shore of the southern sea. There they are joined by Ravana's renegade brother Vibhishana. But they encounter an obstacle on their path. There is a sea they have to cross to reach their destination that is Sri Lanka",
        question: "Can you tell us what is water in the sea composed of?",
        option: [
            "2 O2 + 1/2 H2",
            "2H + 1/2 O2 -> H2O",
            "H + He + Minerals",
            "C + O2",

        ],
        answer: 2,
        
    },
    {
        para: "Jambavan asks the monkeys Nala and Nila to start work on constructing the bridge over the sea. The apes named Nala and Nila construct a floating bridge (known as Rama Setu) across the sea, using stones that floated on water because they had Rama's name written on them. ",

        question: "How many types of rocks are there?",
        option: [
            "3",
            "2",
            "5",
            "4",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "The princes and their army cross over to Lanka. A lengthy war ensues. During a battle, Ravana's son Indrajit hurls a powerful fire weapon at Lakshmana, who is badly wounded.",

        question: "Which of these elements is a major component involved in lighting up a fire?",
        option: [
            "Carbon Dioxide",
            "Nitrogen",
            "Oxygen",            
            "Sodium",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "So Hanuman assumes a gigantic form and flies from Lanka to the Himalayas for taking required medicinal herb for Laxman. ",

        question:
            "As Hanuman moves upwards towards the upper layer of atmosphere, he will soon feel lack of oxygen. To help hanuman, tell us where does atomic oxygen lie in the perodic table?",
        option: [
            "At 8th number. atomic number = 8",
            "At 1th number. atomic number = 1",
            "At 4th number. atomic number = 4",
            "At 7th number. atomic number = 7",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Upon reaching Mount Sumeru, Hanuman was unable to identify the herb that could cure Lakshmana and so decided to bring the entire mountain back to Lanka. ",

        question:
            "What product is obtained as a by-product of photosynthesis performed by plants?",
        option: [
            "Leucine (C6H13NO2)",
            "Glucose (C6H12O6)",
            "Methanol (CH3OH)",
            "carboxyl (COOH)",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        para: "Ravana was having 10 heads depicting his every expression and feeling on each head, Shree Ram tried to kill Ravana ten times by cutting his heads using arrows but nothing use to happen then Rama devotee Vibishan said him to attack on Ravana navel because Ravana navel was full of Amrit which use to help Ravana for surviving and thats why Shree Rama attacked Ravana's navel using Brahmastra and killed Ravana",

        question: "Modern Brahmastra (Nuclear Bomb) is mainly made up of?",
        option: ["Kerosene and Fire", "Helium", "Uranium", "Sulphuric Acid"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        para: "Eventually, the war ends when Rama kills Ravana. ",

        question: "What kind of protein is blood?",
        option: [
            "Globular",
            "Whey Protien",
            "Tertiary",
            "Plant based Protien",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        para: "Then the most awaited moment arrives and Ram happily meets sita.",
        question:
            "When one is happy, endorphin is released in our body. Can you tell us how many endorphin structures are there?",
        option: ["alpha, beta, gamma, sigma", "6-alpha, 7-beta, 8-gamma", "alpha 22-beta", "4, alpha, beta, gamma, sigma"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        para: "On meeting Sita, Rama agrees to Sita's request to undergo an Agni Pariksha (test of fire) to prove her chastity, as he wants to get rid of the rumors surrounding her purity. ",
        question: "How can we stop a fire?",
        option: ["Using CO2", "Using O2", "Using He", "Using Petrol"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {   
        para: "When Sita plunges into the sacrificial fire, Agni, lord of fire raises Sita, unharmed, to the throne, attesting to her innocence.",
        question: "The crown had a ruby. What is the chemical formula for a ruby?",
        option: ["H2SO4", "CO2H2O", "Al2O3", "C9H9N3O2"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];